Loot Amidst the indiscriminate firing, a
thick piece of shell will tear my nose and a
fountain of blood will gush out Sister Ji
darkness fell before my eyes Then all at once he had just
started my first exam when
a bullet went through his head You
and I are lying in my arms
Another bullet went through my heart,
despite immense pain he lay quietly as
if the enemy is with our enemies
And yet it seems, isn't it?
This story of 19-year-old Subedar Major Yogendra Singh Yadav, the youngest soldier to be awarded the Param Vir Chakra, is
more heart-wrenching than any film story.
All our soldiers posted on the border have the
spirit to fight till their last breath.
Divya Dutta with ICICI Bank
salutes this spirit.
In this historic war of actions,
Yadav and his men
stationed at a height of about 70,000 feet were
destroying the enemy by deceiving them and becoming timely.
Due to Abhishek's indiscriminate firing and bombing, our soldiers also suffered heavy losses.  Had to
lift the enemy soldiers fell on the ground Wounded
Indian soldiers Point planted on Yadav
Fighting with a friend Yadav
wrote an important part of the victory of this war Some soldiers kept things in their pockets to
fire at them Gujjars
stopped them were
badly injured and silently
pretending to die With the enemy's strategy,
they studied nearby and
with the smell of their fallen comrades File Shankar got to the enemy
Other parts of the Indian Army reached there and they ran away
Yadav's ordeal was still to come Wounded
by dozens of bullets Body
torn nose and broken Your balance body
Brain crawling waterfalls flowing Yadav paste or
five Commanding Officer of the Indian Army
declared as the enemy's strategy Three days later when I
opened my eyes in the hospital, I came to know that
Tiger Hill Subscribe to Atal Yogendra
Yadav and his entire family I and you
send our oil salute to Quid Pro Just do
a heart salute with a selfie and your
message Half of that www.iocl.com Class
Heart salute ICICI Bank your
emotions Injured after 500 years cheque
[Music]
Yours